The name is **Analee Kasudia**, and the focus is **interaction design and development**. Nice to meet you!

I'm driven by those with a similar appreciation and see the long-term benefits of good design. A decade of experience includes working with both small startups and large organizations, either building a new product or building anew. As a **contractor**, I can work with you or your team's needs in conceptualizing, UI/UX, functional wireframing, visual design, art direction, or HTML/CSS/Javascript. View such examples at **analeekasudia.github.io**.

Outside of design, personal interests include adventures, coffee, progressive house, yoga, dance and kickboxing. Also I'm a part-time student at **General Assembly New York**.

Thank you for your time, and looking forward to your follow-up so we can create something great together. Feel free to email <a href="mailto:akasudia@gmail.com">akasudia@gmail.com</a>, or call 312-317-3545.



#### EXPERIENCE

#### Consultant/Freelancer

October 2015 - Present

- → <u>Teachley.com</u> is undergoing a design revamp of an internal hub, with a launch date in mid-/late-2017.
- → An Air Force squadron needed an updated visual identity. In return, they gave a flag flown during an ongoing operation in Iraq and Syria. Overall, it was a very humbling experience.

# Interaction Design/Code, FORTUNE Magazine

May 2014 - September 2016

→ I worked for and with the smartest editors and writers, focusing on design and code for many editorial projects. It was a mix of interactives, charts, infographics, and creating design templates — some of them firsts for the magazine. Also, design concepts and prototypes were built for more product-based initiatives.

# Lead Designer, DEFY Media/Alloy Digital

August 2012 - March 2014

→ A designer of UI and graphics, for web and mobile apps — in specific, the lead designer of <u>Smosh.com</u>'s redesign. In April 2014, the headquarters was relocated from New York City to Los Angeles.

### **Contract Designer, Teach For America**

November 2011 - September 2012

→ The sole digital designer in their design team. Projects included revamping ~30 infographics shown on their website. The largest overhaul was for <u>teachforamericastore.com</u> — in interface, aesthetics, and HTML/CSS/JQuery. I handled this, and partnered with a project manager to work with external developers for CMS integration.

# Interaction Designer, Carrot

September 2010 - October 2011

→ Web & mobile UI/UX for various major brands, including Red Bull.

### **Independent Designer**

September 2006 - August 2010

→ Projects included web & mobile designs, and HTML/CSS/JQuery for clients such as Comedy Central, Tara Stiles, Signpost, Perk Mobile, Centrl, Hollaback!, and Naganuma Dance.

## Web Designer, Paltalk

April 2007 - December 2008

→ Designed e-newsletters, iconography, an IM client app, and webpages with emphasis on UI.

# Associate Designer, U.S. Mint

January 2004 - December 2005

→ It was an honor to be one of the first, and youngest, designers of the new Artistic Infusion Program. My task was to conceptualize & create dye-ready coin and medallion designs.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Javascript Development, General Assembly New York**

September - November 2016

# B.F.A. in Graphic Design, Columbia College Chicago

→ Includes study abroads to <u>Santa Reparata</u>, Florence, Italy and <u>Hogeschool voor de Kunsten Utrecht</u>, Netherlands.

September 2002 - December 2006